Alec Stone

Phone number 07729542007 Email alecdsstone@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Unity programmer with recent experience in healthcare applications of VR, over 5 years of experience in Unity 3d and over 3 years experience in full stack web development. An early adopter and enthusiast of VR tech. Enjoys collaborating with and learning from interdisciplinary peers. Driven by the buzz of nascent technologies. Thorough learner with a stoic positive attitude. Critical thinker that approaches problems methodically and favours an ordered in approach to work.

SKILLS

- C#, Unity 3D, HDRP, ShaderGraph
- VRTK, Oculus XR, Unity XR, OVR
- Android, Quest debugging
- Photon, UMotion, OBI physics, IBM Watson API
- OOP principles
- PHP, Javascript and Python
- Powershell
- Agile
- Git
- Bash scripting
- Technical documentation

EXPERIENCE

Open University Unity Developer

March 2020 - Present

- Part of an R&D team for healthcare in VR
- Assisted in design and implementation of virtual procedures
- Made reusable systems and tools within Unity for both editor and Play mode
- Developed various key features, following closely to design

Feed Optimise

April 2018 - March 2020

Web Developer

- Extracted and parsed web data for eCommerce feeds
- Built a network of hostable services in aid of core product
- Contributed to development of proprietary services engine
- Gained detailed understanding of back-end and dev ops technologies
- Writes technical documentation in aid of scalability and open source parts of codebase

Alexander Stone 04/02/2020

TFA Marketing

Full Stack Developer

June 2017 - April 2018

- Lead front-end developer on company's new website.
- Creating and maintaining bespoke websites using Laravel, LAMP, PHP, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, JQuery and Vue.
- Ported websites to platforms like Wordpress, Laravel and TFA's own CMS.

Filmology - Sodexo

Feb 2017 - April 2017

Back-end Developer

- Used Python/Scrapy to acquire data on all cinemas in the UK
- Took initiative to implement own solutions and architecture
- Managed research and development into chosen technologies

EDUCATION

Continued Self-Driven Education

Ongoing

• Continued academic progression via Open Source education

CS50 Computer Science

October 2017 - Dec 2017

• A comprehensive foundational overview of CS, mainly using the C programming language.

INTERESTS

- I participate in game jams, VR specific ones if possible
- I dabble in sound and audio engineering
- I play VR games with my girlfriend
- We also make games together

Alexander Stone 04/02/2020